https://sudhanshu.com/policy/

Google
PolicyContact Numbers213 - 985 - 3070(0131) 208 3170(02)- 8003 55708 - 175 - 3670For Other Countries"CALL-BACK (I Will Call You)"UAE & GULFSINGAPOREEUROPE & Other CountriesINDIA & Neighbor CountriesSudhanshu.com Privacy Policy StatementWe at Sudhanshu.com respect your privacy and take the issue of Internet privacy very seriously. By accepting the Sudhanshu.com Terms of Service (as a user of Sudhanshu.com’s services, or through our business solution service) you explicitly consent to the collection, processing, transfer and use and disclosure of any information, including personal information, which you provide to us as outlined in this Privacy Statement, and agree to the terms of our Privacy Statement.As Sudhanshu.com improves its services, we may modify our Privacy Statement at any time without giving you prior notice. By accessing and using our Site and services following any such modifications, you agree to follow and be bound by the Terms of Service as modified. For this reason, we urge you to check here for updates from time to time.Our Privacy Statement addresses the information we collect in connection with both our consumer reading or advice platform (“Astrology Reading, consultation or Advice Service”) and our business solutions platform (“Gems & software Service”). Our treatment of personal information varies for each of our Advice Service and Business Solutions Service.Astrology Reading, consultation or Advice Service: The main purpose of the Sudhanshu.com Astrology Reading, consultation or Advice Service is to provide a platform for consumers to obtain Reading, consultation or advice from Astrologer Dr. Rajendra Raj Sudhanshu via phone or our online text chat service.Online AstrologyVedic AstrologyMedical AstrologyAstrology SoftwareLucky GemsRemediesNakshatraAstrology SignsZodiac Sign
ConsultPolicyTestimonialContactOnline AstrologyVedic AstrologyAstrology ReadingMedical AstrologyAstrology SoftwareLucky GemsRemediesNakshatraAstrology SignsZodiac Sign ConsultPolicyTestimonialContact
Contact Us
(213) 985 3070 (213) 985 3070    (0131) 208 3170 (02) 8003 5570    8175 3670
[recaptcha size:compact]
×
